<marquees>
    <marquee type="language">
        <item name="C#">
            C# was picked up in 2015 in conjunction with Unity. C# has since become the language with
            the highest proficiency, having been used in most developed games, simple console applications, etc.
        </item>
        <item name="C++">
            C++ was first picked up in 2010, during an introductory course to game development
            hosted by Digipen Singapore. Since then, application of C++ has expanded beyond game development
            to areas such as graphics programming in OpenGL.
        </item>
        <item name="HTML5">
            HTML5 was first introduced in the late 2010s, however,
            proper understanding and application of HTML5 was only achieved in 2016.
        </item>
        <item name="CSS3">
            CSS3 was first introduced alongside HTML5 in the late 2010s. Similarly, proficiency in CSS3
            only developed in 2016.
        </item>
        <item name="JavaScript">
            JavaScript was picked up in 2016, being one of the tested components
            in the WorldSkills Singapore competition. JavaScript remains a core component in most,
            if not all, web development projects to date.
        </item>
        <item name="PHP">
            PHP was picked up in 2015, being another tested component in the WorldSkills Singapore competition.
            Use of PHP in web development has increased dramatically since,
            serving as a core component in larger web applications.
        </item>
        <item name="SQL">
            SQL was picked up in 2015, first used in a school subject, Database and Information Systems.
            Use of SQL then expanded to the WorldSkills Singapore competition.
        </item>
    </marquee>
    <marquee type="framework">
        <item name="Bootstrap">
            Bootstrap was picked up in 2016 as a quick way to create decent looking layouts for the web.
            Since then, with increased proficiency in HTML and CSS,
            Bootstrap has seen less use in web development projects.
        </item>
        <item name="jQuery">
            jQuery was picked up in 2016, being a tested skill in the WorldSkills Singapore competition.
            Since then, jQuery has been used for many web projects,
            both pertaining WorldSkills as well as external projects.
        </item>
        <item name="Laravel 5.2">
            Laravel 5.2 was picked up in 2016, being yet another tested skill in the WorldSkills Singapore competition.
            Although many intricacies of the framework are still yet to be discovered,
            proficiency in Laravel has reached the point
            where it has proven to be a powerful asset for websites and web applications.
        </item>
        <item name="OpenGL">
            OpenGL was picked up in 2016 as a library used in school curriculum
            for the subjects Game Math and Physics, and Graphics Programming.
        </item>
    </marquee>
    <marquee type="program">
        <item name="Unity">
            Unity was first picked up in 2015, and has become the primary choice of game engine for game development.
            Since then, several games made with Unity have been published on various platforms.
        </item>
        <item name="GameMaker">
            GameMaker - as well as its successor GameMaker Studio - was picked up in 2013.
            Initially using the drag-and-drop method, and later using primarily Game Maker Language (GML),
            GameMaker served as a tool for creating several unpublished game prototypes.
        </item>
        <item name="FL Studio">
            FL Studio has been and is still being used as the go-to program for music composition.
            Although there is still much to learn, several songs have already been composed
            and published on Soundcloud or used in various games.
        </item>
        <item name="Adobe Photoshop">
            Adobe Photoshop is the primary tool used for image editing and manipulation.
        </item>
        <item name="Adobe Illustrator">
            Adobe Illustrator is the de facto standard for creating vector illustrations.
            Illustrator has been used in the past to create graphics for various games, artwork, websites, etc.
        </item>
        <item name="Blender 3D">
            Blender 3D was picked up as a hobby in 2012.
            Blender remains as the primary tool for creating 3D art,
            even despite the introduction of Autodesk Maya and Cinema 4D.
        </item>
        <item name="Autodesk Maya">
            Autodesk Maya was picked up in 2016 as a component of a school subject.
            Maya was used for several school subjects during enrolment in Temasek Polytechnic.
        </item>
        <item name="Autodesk Mudbox">
            Autodesk Mudbox was used in conjunction with Autodesk Maya for 3D texturing in 2016.
            Mudbox was used once for a school assignment in the subject Game Texture, Lighting and Animation.
        </item>
        <item name="Cinema 4D">
            Cinema 4D was picked up in 2013 as part of a school subject, Creative 3D Animation.
            Cinema 4D was used in the creation of a short animation coursework,
            which is unfortunately no longer available for viewing.
        </item>
    </marquee>
</marquees>